[
  {
    "question": "la agencia de viajes",
    "answer": "die Reiseagentur"
  },
  {
    "question": "la agencia",
    "answer": "die Agentur"
  },
  {
    "question": "el centro de la ciudad",
    "answer": "das Stadtzentrum"
  },
  {
    "question": "el viaje",
    "answer": "die Reise"
  },
  {
    "question": "el día",
    "answer": "der Tag"
  },
  {
    "question": "la reunión",
    "answer": "das Meeting"
  },
  {
    "question": "la oficina",
    "answer": "das Büro"
  },
  {
    "question": "el cliente",
    "answer": "der Kunde"
  },
  {
    "question": "el colega",
    "answer": "der Kollege"
  },
  {
    "question": "el turista",
    "answer": "der Tourist"
  },
  {
    "question": "la colega",
    "answer": "die Kollegin"
  },
  {
    "question": "los gastos de viaje",
    "answer": "die Reisekosten"
  },
  {
    "question": "la reserva",
    "answer": "die Reservierung"
  },
  {
    "question": "el hotel",
    "answer": "das Hotel"
  },
  {
    "question": "el trabajo",
    "answer": "die Arbeit"
  },
  {
    "question": "la mañana",
    "answer": "der Morgen"
  },
  {
    "question": "la bicicleta",
    "answer": "das Fahrrad"
  },
  {
    "question": "el coche",
    "answer": "das Auto"
  },
  {
    "question": "el minuto",
    "answer": "die Minute"
  },
  {
    "question": "el pie",
    "answer": "der Fuß"
  },
  {
    "question": "el tren",
    "answer": "der Zug"
  },
  {
    "question": "la tarde",
    "answer": "der Abend"
  },
  {
    "question": "el perro",
    "answer": "der Hund"
  },
  {
    "question": "el amigo",
    "answer": "der Freund"
  },
  {
    "question": "el viernes",
    "answer": "der Freitag"
  },
  {
    "question": "el restaurante",
    "answer": "das Restaurant"
  },
  {
    "question": "la casa",
    "answer": "das Haus"
  },
  {
    "question": "el niño",
    "answer": "das Kind"
  },
  {
    "question": "el hombre",
    "answer": "der Mann"
  },
  {
    "question": "el kebab",
    "answer": "der Kebab"
  },
  {
    "question": "el parque",
    "answer": "der Park"
  },
  {
    "question": "trabajar",
    "answer": "arbeiten"
  },
  {
    "question": "estar situado",
    "answer": "liegen"
  },
  {
    "question": "planear",
    "answer": "planen"
  },
  {
    "question": "vender",
    "answer": "verkaufen"
  },
  {
    "question": "empezar",
    "answer": "beginnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "telefonear",
    "answer": "telefonieren"
  },
  {
    "question": "venir",
    "answer": "kommen"
  },
  {
    "question": "llamarse",
    "answer": "heißen"
  },
  {
    "question": "hacer",
    "answer": "machen"
  },
  {
    "question": "conducir",
    "answer": "fahren"
  },
  {
    "question": "vivir",
    "answer": "wohnen"
  },
  {
    "question": "necesitar",
    "answer": "brauchen"
  },
  {
    "question": "ir",
    "answer": "gehen"
  },
  {
    "question": "jugar",
    "answer": "spielen"
  },
  {
    "question": "comer",
    "answer": "essen"
  },
  {
    "question": "cocinar",
    "answer": "kochen"
  }
]
